Finding Aid for Satakunta Region immigrant letters, 1880-1964
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Parkano, letters to
  - Lyydia Lahtinen
    - from: Leo Lahti. Ont. Ind., 1947-1955; 7 items (Reel 19)
  - Helga Laine
    - from: Tyyne Laine. Ont., 1946-1964; 6 items (Reel 19)
  - Aino Rintamäki
    - from: J. Wuori. Minn., 1963-1964; 3 items (Reel 19)
  - Bertta Selin
    - from: Martta Telkkinen. Ont., 1931-1946; 5 items (Reel 19)
  - Helmi Toivonen
    - from: J. Walli. N.Y.
      - Conn., 1923-1951; 9 items (Reel 19)
      - Detroit, Mich., 1951; 1 items (Reel 19)
      - Conn., Cal., 1954-1964; 14 items (Reel 19)
  - Niilo Isoaho
    - from: Olga Pihlaja. Minn., 1938-1939; 6 items (Reel 19)
  - Elsa Mäkynen
    - from: Elna Niemi
      - Marquette, Mich., 1961-1962; 2 items (Reel 19)
      - N.J., Ont., 1948-1951; 3 items (Reel 19)
      - Marquette, Mich., 1961; 1 items (Reel 19)
      - Ont., Minn., 1951-1963; 9 items (Reel 19)
      - Marquette, Mich., 1963; 3 items (Reel 19)
      - Minn., 1950; 2 items (Reel 19)
      - Munising, Mich., 1951; 3 items (Reel 19)
      - Minn., 1959; 1 items (Reel 19)
      - Marquette, Mich., 1962; 1 items (Reel 19)
      - Minn., 1963; 3 items (Reel 19)
      - Munising, Mich., 1950-1963; 5 items (Reel 19)
      - Minn., 1964; 1 items (Reel 19)
      - Munising, Mich., undated; 1 items (Reel 19)
    - from: Pirkko Venetjoki
      - Marquette, Mich., Ishpeming, Mich, 1961-1964; 60 items (Reel 20)
      - Plinn., Fla., 1960-1964; 5 items (Reel 20)
  - Lilja Kuusisto
    - from: Linne Marttila. Minn., 1957; 13 items (Reel 20)
  - Lyydia Laurila
    - from: Linne Kontturi. Ont., Wash., 1960-1963; 12 items (Reel 20)
  - Lempi Tarkki
    - from: Hilma Klee. N.Y., 1963-1964; 2 items (Reel 20)
  - Niilo Paavilainen
    - from: Aino Hutton. Mass., N.Y., Wis., 1954-1964; 14 items (Reel 20)
  - Helmi Lystilä
    - from: Vaino Kantola. Oregon., Alaska (2, 1962 (Reel 20)
  - Elsa Leppänen
    - from: Esteri Gustavson. N.Y., 1939-1947; 19 items (Reel 20)
    - from: Toini Salmenoja. N.Y., 1949; 2 items (Reel 20)
  - Toivo Yliruusi
    - from: Pentti Yliruusi. B.C., 1959-1964; 15 items (Reel 20)
  - Rauni Järvinen
    - from: Tuori Elo. Ont., 1947-1964; 6 items (Reel 20)
- Pomarkku, letters to
  - Suoma Mäkelä
    - from: Elma Haltunen. Ishpeming,Mich., Negaunee, Mich., 1957-1963; 4 items (Reel 20)
  - Hilja Santala
    - from: Rauha Heino. Minn., 1954-1959; 5 items (Reel 20)
  - Impi Kaseva
    - from: Selma Lammi. Minn., Fla., 1949-1957; 7 items (Reel 20)
  - Frans Kivelä
    - from: Anton Palmquist. Wis., Minn., 1948-1964; 6 items (Reel 20)
  - Paavo Koskela
    - from: sister. N.Y., 1956-1962; 23 items (Reel 20)
    - from unnamed., undated; 4 items (Reel 20)
    - from: Vera Kaini., undated; 1 items (Reel 20)
    - from: Alina Kopra. Fla., 1957; 2 items (Reel 20)
    - from: unnamed., 1960; 3 items (Reel 20)
  - Tyyne Koskinen
    - from: Oskari Hautamaki. Minn., Ont., 1963; 8 items (Reel 20)
  - Selma Elonen
    - from: Aune Paavola. Ont., 1962-1964; 5 items (Reel 20)
    - from: Tyyne Kiiskinen. Ont., 1963-1964; 10 items (Reel 20)
- City of Pori and Pori rural parish, letters to
  - Gösta Broman
    - from: Emil Broman. Rudyard, Mich., 1946; 1 items (Reel 20)
  - Helmi Broman
    - from: Tekla Snall. N.H., 1946; 4 items (Reel 20)
    - from: Tekla Jalonen. Maine, 1947-1952; 5 items (Reel 20)
  - Aili Stenholm
    - from: Herman Lehto. Minn., 1952; 1 items (Reel 20)
  - Johan Mannila
    - from: Jalmar Mannila
      - Ont., 1930; 1 items (Reel 20)
      - Detroit, Mich., 1960-1964; 14 items (Reel 20)
  - Raija Lehtonen
    - from: Isak Nordlund. Fla., 1956-1963; 8 items (Reel 20)
  - Vieno Willman
    - from: Esteri Gronlund. B.C., 1924; 1 items (Reel 20)
  - Rauha Niskanen
    - from: Lempi Besio. S.D., N.D., 1958-1961; 3 items (Reel 20)
  - Anni Salonen
    - from: Eero Langen. England, Tex., Ont., Mass., 1922-1963; 12 items (Reel 20)
  - Enne Nordling
    - from: Heikki Lauren. Quebec, 1957-1963; 18 items (Reel 20)
  - Lahja Täckman
    - from: Rauha Dechenes. N.H., 1961-1964; 2 items (Reel 20)
    - from: Raili Hankilammi. Ont., Mass., 1960-1964; 7 items (Reel 20)
    - from: Anna-Liisa Vallin. Mass., N.Y., 1961-1964; 6 items (Reel 20)
  - Martta Grönvall
    - from: Aune Loflund. B.C., 1961-1963; 2 items (Reel 20)
  - Yrjö Nordling
    - from: Lauri Nordling. Soviet Union, 1953-1959; 9 items (Reel 20)
  - Bror Roos
    - from: various. N.Y., 1963-1964; 11 items (Reel 20)
  - Maria Ahl
    - from: Eila Ahonen. Que, Ont., Ore., 1952-1961; 16 items (Reel 20)
  - Anja Hankilammi
    - from: Raili Jacoby. Maine, N.H., Mass., 1956-1963; 9 items (Reel 20)
  - Liisa Hankilammi
    - from: unnamed. Mass., 1962-1963; 4 items (Reel 20)
    - from: Anna-Liisa Wallin. Maine, N.Y., 1961-1962; 2 items (Reel 20)
  - Hilkka Raita
    - from: Sirkka Kotilehti. Ont., 1964; 1 items (Reel 20)
    - from: Ritva Perala. Ont., 1964; 1 items (Reel 20)
- Punkalaidun, letters to
  - Elma Säteri
    - from: Naimi Elvgren. N.Y., 1953; 3 items (Reel 20)
    - from: Elsa Joki. Ont., 1923-1963; 27 items (Reel 20)
    - from: Rosa Hakojarvi. N.J., R.I., 1946-1963; 29 items (Reel 21)
    - from: Helmi Ranta. R.I., 1955-1969; 10 items (Reel 21)
- City of Rauma and Rauma rural parish, letters to
  - Lauri Aikko
    - from: Eelis Nygren. Wash., 1955-1958; 3 items (Reel 21)
  - Aune Lehtisalo
    - from: Hilma Pehkonen. N.Y., 1919; 2 items (Reel 21)
    - from: Lilja Wirmalainen, N.J., 1957; 3 items (Reel 21)
    - from: Anna Pehkonen. N.J., 1928; 2 items (Reel 21)
  - Sylvi Aikko
    - from: Aina Stenfors. Calif., 1957-1964; 6 items (Reel 21)
  - Vihtori Varjonen
    - from: Frans Saarnijoki. Nova Scotia, 1924-1928; 6 items (Reel 21)
    - from: unnamed. Ont., 1947; 1 items (Reel 21)
  - Viljo Uusi-Osmi
    - from: Emil Hellsten. Ont., 1962-1964; 6 items (Reel 21)
  - Lauri Aikko
    - from: Charles Austin. Fla., 1960; 6 items (Reel 21)
  - Hannes Kuusisto
    - from: Frans Kuusisto. B.C., 1959; 1 items (Reel 21)
    - from: Vera Kuusisto. Cal., 1960-1961; 6 items (Reel 21)
  - Olavi Marva
    - from: Taimi Tanew., 1964; 1 items (Reel 21)
  - Eine Trogen
    - from: Aili Saari. Oregon., Wash., 1915-1957; 16 items (Reel 21)
    - from: Emil Hannula. Maine, N.Y., 1919-1923; 6 items (Reel 21)
    - from: Yrjo Salo. Manitoba, 1928; 2 items (Reel 21)
    - from: Werner Lehtisalo. Ont., 1924; 1 items (Reel 21)
  - Aino Kuusisto
    - from: Sandra Tervonen. N.J. (l items), 1960 (Reel 21)
    - from: Ida Luntta. Conn., 1963; 1 items (Reel 21)
    - from: Ester Virtanen., 1962; 2 items (Reel 21)
    - photos, 10 items (Reel 21)
    - from: Martta Maki. Crystal Falls, Mich., 1958-1963; 4 items (Reel 21)
    - from: Elina Makkonen. Md., 1960; 1 items (Reel 21)
    - from: Saida Williams. N.J., 1958; 2 items (Reel 21)
  - Aidi Salminen
    - from: Mari Haapala. Conn., N.Y., 1949-1957; 11 items (Reel 21)
  - Hermi Suomela
    - from: Iisakki Apola. Australia, 1962-1963; 4 items (Reel 21)
  - Sandra Lindquist
    - from: Anton Vahlroos. Mass., 1948; 2 items (Reel 21)
  - Aina Lehtonen
    - from: Ellen Jalo. Fl., 1961; 5 items (Reel 21)
  - H. Granroos
    - from: Jenny Ruohonen. New Zea, 1964; 2 items (Reel 21)
    - from: S. Granroos. New Zea, 1963; 3 items (Reel 21)
  - Juho Suoja
    - from: Aarne Suoja. Alta., 1954-1963; 5 items (Reel 21)
  - Selma Malinen
    - from: Matti Saari. B.C., 1963-1964; 2 items (Reel 21)
  - Sylvi Aikk
    - from: Alli Niskanen. New Zea, 1953-1963; 5 items (Reel 21)
  - Anni Simpanen
    - from: Jalmar Lehtonen. Australia, 1958-1962; 2 items (Reel 21)
- Siikainen, letters to
  - Sofia Heikkilä
    - from: Frans Koivisto
      - Ont., 1889; 1 items (Reel 21)
      - Detroit, Mich., Gwinn, Mich., Highland Park,. Mich., Forsyth, Mich., 1948-1959; 4 items (Reel 21)
      - Ont., 1958; 3 items (Reel 21)
      - Detroit, Mich., 1952; 1 items (Reel 21)
  - Jenny Vanhatalo
    - from: V.J. Laaksonen. B.C
      - Minn., Kansas, Wis., 1948-1955; 48 items (Reel 21)
      - Negaunee, Mich., Ishpeming, Mich., 1896-1955; 14 items (Reel 21)
      - Wis., 1934-1950; 28 items (Reel 21)
  - Simo Oksa
    - from: Robert Oksa. Ont., Mass., N.H., 1903-1949; 36 items (Reel 21)
  - Werner Koivunen
    - from: Alina Hallam. Calif., N.Y., 1919; 6 items (Reel 21)
    - from: Victor Koivunen. Minn., 1922-1927; 3 items (Reel 21)
    - from: Johan Koivunen. N.Y., 1957-1959; 3 items (Reel 21)
  - Ville Hakamäki
    - from: Frans Hakamaki. Negaunee, Mich., 1906; 1 items (Reel 21)
    - from: Kalle Hakamaki. Quebec, Ont., 1932-1961; 5 items (Reel 21)
    - from: Frans Hakamaki. Ont., 1963; 3 items (Reel 21)
  - Frans Niemi
    - from: Oskar Lampi. Ohio, Wash., N.Y., 1956-1961; 3 items (Reel 21)
  - Heikki Heikkilä
    - from: Anton Anttila. Minn., 1956; 1 items (Reel 21)
    - from: Hilda Maki. N.Y., 1951; 1 items (Reel 21)
    - from: Armas Aijaja. N.H., 1962; 1 items (Reel 21)
  - Emilia Myllymäki
    - from: Jenny Talo. Rock, Mich., 1947; 1 items (Reel 21)
    - from: Laura Takala. Ont., undated; 1 items (Reel 21)
    - from: Mari Korpi. Ohio, 1962; 1 items (Reel 21)
  - Tyyra Virkki
    - from: Katri Svord. Mass., 1954; 15 items (Reel 21)
    - from: Helmi Killian. Fla., 1955-1962; 6 items (Reel 21)
    - from: Anni Niemi. Minn., 1958-1963; 12 items (Reel 21)
  - Kaija Ahlros
    - from: Alina Hallam. N.Y., 1936-1962; 8 items (Reel 21)
  - Hilma Tammelin
    - from: Nestor Jokinen
      - Detroit, Mich., Ironwood, Mich., 1941-1961; 7 items (Reel 21)
      - Fla., 1962; 1 items (Reel 21)
      - Ironwood, Mich., 1962; 1 items (Reel 21)
  - Unknown Recipient
    - from: Rakel Syrjala. Mass., 1957-?, 7 items (Reel 21)
  - Väinö Anttila
    - from: Veera Tolvanen. Bessemer, Mich., undated; 1 items (Reel 21)
    - from: Jalmar Elo. Dukes, Mich., undated; 1 items (Reel 21)
    - from: Katri Tonttila. Ill., 1924; 1 items (Reel 21)
  - Lyydi Kiviniemi
    - from: Hilma Lahti. Wash., 1952; 1 items (Reel 21)
  - Josefiina Pitkäranta
    - from: Tekla Tulla. Mass., 1956; 3 items (Reel 21)
  - Fiina Sulkava
    - from: Selim Maki. Sask., Ont., 1937-1956; 3 items (Reel 21)
  - Senja Jaakkola
    - from: Ida Grandberg. N.Y., 1962-1964; 5 items (Reel 21)
  - Olga Lähteenkorva
    - from: H. Saari. Mass., 1948-1969; 22 items (Reel 22)
  - Aili Mattila
    - from: Emilia Uusitalo. Crystal Falls, Mich., 1963; 1 items (Reel 22)
  - Aino Niemi
    - from: Sofia Kendal. Marquette, Mich., 1963; 1 items (Reel 22)
  - Heikki Soini
    - from: Kalle Soini. N.Y., 1953-1961; 6 items (Reel 22)
    - from: Nestor Lampinen. Australia, N.Y., 1951-1962; 10 items (Reel 22)
  - Miina Uutaniemi
    - from: Arttur Niemi. Minn., 1936-1947; 6 items (Reel 22)
  - Selma Uutaniemi
    - from: Arttur Niemi. Minn., 1947; 3 items (Reel 22)
  - Heikki Laakso
    - from: Alma Hill. Minn., 1945-1952; 11 items (Reel 22)
  - Jalmari Sulkava
    - from: Hilma Myllymaki. N.Y., N.J., Ont., 1915-1922; 18 items (Reel 22)
  - Hugo Uutaniemi
    - from: H.G. Lammi. Minn., Fla., 1930-1969; 4 items (Reel 22)
  - Vilhelmiina Uutaniemi
    - from: H.A. Lammi. Minn., 1945-1948; 3 items (Reel 22)
  - Emmii Viitanen
    - from: Ruura Kratt. Winona, Mich., 1956-1963; 4 items (Reel 22)
    - from: Ida Saari. Winona, Mich., 1953-1954; 6 items (Reel 22)
    - from: unnamed. Winona, Mich., 1956; 1 items (Reel 22)
  - Pauliina Anttila
    - from: Josefina Niemi. Marquette, Mich., 1962-1964; 14 items (Reel 22)
  - Ida Eloranta
    - from: Heikki Norkoli. Mass., undated; 3 items (Reel 22)
    - from: Wille Norkoli., undated; 1947; 1 items (Reel 22)
  - Hilma Kangasniemi
    - from: Amanda Syvanen. Fla., 1964; 1 items (Reel 22)
  - Tuovi Kariniemi
    - from: Milja Jalo. Ohio (4 items, 1963-1964 (Reel 22)
  - Ida Laine
    - from: Sandra Lasonen., undated; 3 items (Reel 22)
  - Frans Luoma
    - from: Ida Granberg. N.Y., 1953-1959; 5 items (Reel 22)
  - Väinö Luoma
    - from: Ida Granberg. N.Y., 1940-1963; 44 items (Reel 22)
  - Selma Rajala
    - from: Alma Tamminen. Minn., 1959; 1 items (Reel 22)
  - Elviida Viljanen
    - from: Charles Makke. Calif., 1961; 1 items (Reel 22)
    - from: Hilma Myllymaki. N.Y., 1948; 1 items (Reel 22)
    - from: Robert Maki. Ohio, 1962; 2 items (Reel 22)
  - Paavo Alinentalo
    - from: Aina Salmi. Newberry, Mich., 1964; 1 items (Reel 22)
  - Emilia Lepistö
    - from: Hilja Toikka. Ont., N.J., 1960-1964; 4 items (Reel 22)
    - from Lydia Knut. Wash., 1947-1962; 2 items (Reel 22)
  - Selma Kalliomäki
    - from: Milja Hartson. N.Y., Conn., 1950-1962; 6 items (Reel 22)
  - Lempi Korpela
    - from: Amanda Syvanen., 1955; 7 items (Reel 22)
  - Heikki Lehtiniemi
    - from: Selma Silvennoinen. N.Y., 1963; 1 items (Reel 22)
  - Villehard Mäkinen
    - from: Lyydi Linko. N.Y., Minn., 1946-1962; 3 items (Reel 22)
  - Impi Viinamäki
    - from: Amanda Syvanen. N.Y., 1959; 1 items (Reel 22)
  - Aili Lähteenmäki
    - from: Jenny Ranta. Maine, 1963-1964; 9 items (Reel 22)
  - Lahja Niemi
    - from: Aina Barlund. Alta., 1956-1964; 5 items (Reel 22)
  - Mikko Anttila
    - from: Johan Erkintalo. Bessemer, Mich., 1945-1952; 2 items (Reel 22)
    - from: Veera Tolvanen. Bessemer, Mich., 1951; 2 items (Reel 22)
  - Asser Erkkilä
    - from: various
      - Negaunee, Mich., undated; 1 items (Reel 22)
      - N.Y., undated; 1 items (Reel 22)
      - Marquette, Mich., 1963; 1 items (Reel 22)
      - N.H., 1962; 1 items (Reel 22)
      - Negaunee, Mich., 1962; 3 items (Reel 22)
      - N.Y., N.H., Ill., Fla., 1949-1961; 10 items (Reel 22)
      - photos (Reel 22)
  - Suoma Korpela
    - from: Olga Dietrich, 1963; 3 items (Reel 22)
  - Katri Lähteenmäki
    - from: Eino Honkanen. Pickford, Mich., Newberry, Mich., Detroit, Mich., Highland Park, Mich., 1932-1947; 4 items (Reel 22)
  - Aini Mustakangas
    - from: Robert Korpi. Minn., 1959-1969; 2 items (Reel 22)
  - Hilja Mäkitalo
    - from: I. Jarvenpaa. Ont., 1955-1959; 2 items (Reel 22)
  - Vieno Nummi
    - from: Martin Kotiranta. Minn., 1958-1961; 4 items (Reel 22)
  - Juho Peltomäki
    - from: Josefina Niemi. Marquette, Mich., Caspian, Mich., Rumely, Mich., 1926-1962; 117 items (Reel 22)
  - Juho Rajala
    - from: Gust Peterson
      - Calumet, Mich., 1962-1963; 2 items (Reel 22)
      - Ont., undated; 4 items (Reel 22)
    - from: Senja Torttila. Ont., undated; 4 items (Reel 22)
  - Tilda Vanhatalo
    - from: Emilia Helminen. Minn., 1952-1963; 6 items (Reel 23)
  - Sulo Viljanen
    - from: Wihtori Myllymaki
      - Forsyth, Mich., 1904; 2 items (Reel 23)
      - Minn., Ont., N.Y., Cal., 1904-1946; 36 items (Reel 23)
  - Richard Ylinen
    - from: Juho Hemajoki
      - Ohio, 1900; 1 items (Reel 23)
      - Negaunee, Mich., Rock, Mich., 1914-1931; 9 items (Reel 23)
  - Elsa Myllymäki
    - from: Olga Haapanen. Mass., undated; 1 items (Reel 23)
  - Tilda. Tonttila
    - from: Hilma Palmu. Germany, Fla., 1934-1964; 3 items (Reel 23)
  - Maija Koskinen
    - from: Katherine Anderson. Ill., 1963-1964; 3 items (Reel 23)
    - from: Anna-Liisa Koskinen. Ill., N.Y., Fla., 1962-1963; 6 items (Reel 23)
  - Milja Myllymäki
    - from: Olga Maki. B.C., 1964; 4 items (Reel 23)
  - Urho Rantala
    - from: Lempi Saine. Minn., 1948-1969; 7 items (Reel 23)
  - Agnes Heikkilä
    - from: Veikko Mahlamaki. Ont., 1959-1962; 8 items (Reel 23)
  - Mr. Westergard
    - from: Alma Nygard. Ont., Minn., Mass., N.Y., Conn., B.C., 1908-1937; 25 items (Reel 23)
  - A. Isokorpi
    - from: Helmi Aho. Ont., 1955; 1 items (Reel 23)
    - from: Raija Kujansuu. Australia, 1958; 1 items (Reel 23)
  - Elli Talasterä
    - from: Jenny Makinen. N.Y., 1963-1964; 2 items (Reel 23)
    - from: Eeva Lampinen. N.Y., 1962-1963; 5 items (Reel 23)
  - Alma Inkinen
    - from: Raija Kujansuu. Australia, 1958-1963; 3 items (Reel 23)
  - Elsa Myllymäki
    - from: Hilma Gass. Mass., 1961-1963; 6 items (Reel 23)
  - Hilkka Hovi
    - from: Orvokki Tuomikoski. Australia (l items), 1963 (Reel 23)
  - Olga Lähteenkorva
    - from: Helena Haavisto. Australia, 1962-1964; 4 items (Reel 23)
  - Eino Erkkilä
    - from: Ellen Lindroos. Ill., 1954-1963; 38 items (Reel 23)
  - Yrjö Kuusinen
    - from: Lydia Tobias.
      - Ill., 1963; 1 items (Reel 23)
      - Lansing, Mich., 1958; 2 items (Reel 23)
  - Elli Starck
    - from: Helvi Nelson. Ill., 1963; 2 items (Reel 23)
  - Sandra Ylinen
    - from: Ellen Lindroos.
      - Kaleva, Mich., 1946; 2 items (Reel 23)
      - Ill., 1947-1954; 5 items (Reel 23)
  - Unknown Recipient
    - from: N. Erkkila
      - Ishpeming, Mich., undated; 1 items (Reel 23)
      - Ill., 1926; 1 items (Reel 23)
    - from: unnamed
      - Ironwood, Mich., 1955; 1 items (Reel 23)
      - Fla., 1963-1964; 2 items (Reel 23)
- Suodenniemi, letters to
  - Matilda Saarikoski
    - from: Isak Pihlajakoski. Gladstone, Mich., Newberry, Mich., 1904-1921; 3 items (Reel 23)
  - Anni Lehtinen
    - from: Sofia Kannisto. Calif., 1958; 2 items (Reel 23)
  - Lauri Kivimäki
    - from: Tilda Heino. Minn., 1951-1958; 3 items (Reel 23)
  - Mauri Vihusaari
    - from: Saima Kuivila. Negaunee, Mich, 1949-1962; 2 items (Reel 23)
  - Helga Lähteenmäki
    - from: Hilma Linfors. Minn., 1962-1964; 4 items (Reel 23)
  - Kustaa Holma
    - from: E.S. Burrington. Minn., 1953-1964; 5 items (Reel 23)
  - Fiina Kivikoski
    - from: Marie Ronning. N.Y., 1946-1958; 11 items (Reel 23)
  - Anna Lehtonen
    - from: Eevert Myllymaa. Minn., 1946-1953; 2 items (Reel 23)
  - Frans Nieminen
    - from: Vihtori Niemi. N.H., 1913-1956; 51 items (Reel 23)
    - from: Tilda Himottu. Mass., 1921-1950; 26 items (Reel 23)
    - from: Ellen Broden. Michigan, 1916-1936; 47 items (Reel 23)
  - Anna Löytömäki
    - from: Eeva Rantanen. Cal., 1949-1956; 5 items (Reel 23)
  - Maria Takala
    - from: Hilma Linfors. Minn., 1950-1963; 6 items (Reel 23)
  - Elsa Kahila
    - from: Tilda Heino, Arne Heino. Ill., 1946-1964; 22 items (Reel 23)
  - Taimi Aalto
    - from: Lauri Teinila. Minn., 1939-1948; 2 items (Reel 23)
  - Elli Jokiranta
    - from: Frans Niittenmaa. Mass., 1947; 1 items (Reel 23)
  - Aili Kahila
    - from: Aili Stromholm. Mass., 1958-1963; 3 items (Reel 23)
  - Lyydia Elovaara
    - from: Eemil Elovaara. Mass., Canada, 1913-1928; 7 items (Reel 23)
  - Eila Nevanpää
    - from: William Naal. Mass., Minn., 1949-1958; 10 items (Reel 23)
  - Ellen Luoju
    - from: Oskari Lilja. Fla., 1948-1964; 5 items (Reel 24)
  - Herman Korkeamäki
    - from: Herman Korkeamaki. Minn., B.C., 1911-1936; 6 items (Reel 24)
  - Reino Lamminen
    - from: K. Lahti. Minn., 1934; 1 items (Reel 24)
  - Aira Mäkinen
    - from: Bernhard Tarvainen. Mass., 1 items (Reel 24)
  - Elli Koskinen
    - from: Lauri Lampi. Ont., 1949-1964; 6 items (Reel 24)
  - Anni Leppäjärvi
    - from: Lauri Saari. Mass., 1961; 1 items (Reel 24)
  - Eino Seppä
    - from: Lauri Saari. Mass., 1935; 1 items (Reel 24)
  - Flina Aijö
    - from: Jalmari Kaasalainen. Ont., 1961; 1 items (Reel 24)
- Säkylä, letters to
  - Kerttu Polvi
    - from: Tilda Liikaluoma. Ohio, 1898-1950; 12 items (Reel 24)
    - from: John Laaksonen. Pa., Ohio, 1922; 2 items (Reel 24)
    - from: Manda Laaksonen. Ohio, Fla., 1902-1940; 13 items (Reel 24)
    - from: Erland Seppala. Sask., 1917; 1 items (Reel 24)
    - from: Hilja Seppala. Sask., 1939; 1 items (Reel 24)
  - Elli Palmula
    - from: Tekla Wilen. Minn., 1950; 2 items (Reel 24)
    - from: Helmi Bostrom. Ont. Cl items), 1962 (Reel 24)
  - Unto Vallin
    - from: Vilho Vallin. Minn., 1949-1959; 12 items (Reel 24)
  - Hilma Kaunisto
    - from: Hilda Niemi. Ont., 1962-1964; 2 items (Reel 24)
  - Regina Ojala
    - from: Hulda Lindstrom, Anna Virtanen. photo, 1 items (Reel 24)
  - Kerttu Kankare
    - from: Hilma Julin. Wash., 1951; 2 items (Reel 24)
    - from: Blonda Tuuri. Minn., 1931-1940; 6 items (Reel 24)
    - from: Edna Marion. Minn., 1929-1962; 15 items (Reel 24)
  - Helmi Koivisto
    - from: Fanny Kulmala. N.Y., Mass., 1908-1912; 12 items (Reel 24)
  - Alma Rauvola
    - from: various. N.H., Vt., D.C., Mass., Tex., N.H., 1909-1964; 33 items (Reel 24)
  - Iivari Heinonen
    - from: Jack Hansen. N.Y., Conn., 1958-1964; 7 items (Reel 24)
  - Fanni Välilä
    - from: unnamed. Photos, 3 items (Reel 24)
  - Amanda Sepänjoki
    - from: Hulda Lindstrom. N.Y., 1949-1963; 13 items (Reel 24)
  - Iivari Heinonen
    - from: Allen Hansen. Philippines, 1963; 2 items (Reel 24)
  - Hilma Koskinen
    - from: Vilho Valli. Minn., 1954-1963; 20 items (Reel 24)
  - Amanda Sepänjoki
    - from: Valma Hakala. N.Y., R.I., 1947-1959; 4 items (Reel 24)
  - Anna Vahala
    - from: Martta Selin. Manitoba, 1963; 2 items (Reel 24)
  - Taimi. Salminen
    - from: Kyllikki Koskenoia. Ont., 1950-1964; 7 items (Reel 24)
  - Marja-Leena Kaunisto
    - from: Hilkka Sulkava. Eng, 1961; 1 items (Reel 24)
- Tyrvää-Vammala, letters to
  - Tyyne Pohjola
    - from: August Nordling. N.J., Fla., 1899-1952; 9 items (Reel 24)
  - Oskari Pykälä
    - from: Ville Pykala. Oregon., Wash., 1932-1936; 8 items (Reel 24)
  - Ina Hyrkki
    - from: Juho Lahtinen. Wis., Wash., 1909-1919; 2 items (Reel 24)
  - Herman Korkiamäki
    - from: Katri Tiusanen. N.J., 1935-1964; 8 items (Reel 24)
  - Oskari Pykälä
    - from: Kalle Pykala
      - Negaunee, Mich., 1910-1914; 10 items (Reel 24)
      - Oregon., 1919-1930; 2 items (Reel 24)
      - Negaunee, Mich., 1910-1912; 6 items (Reel 24)
- Vampula, letters to
  - Olga Juurakko-oja
    - from: Ida Vesanen. Conn., 1962-1964; 2 items (Reel 24)
  - Aili Travanti
    - from: Hilma Wirkkala. Wash., 1963; 2 items (Reel 24)
- Outside Satakunta province, letters to
  - Helsinki
    - Maija Ritvanen
      - from: Ester Gustavson. N.Y., R.I., Mass., Ont., 1938-1962; 44 items (Reel 24)
  - Lauritsa
    - Susanna Lemblin
      - from: Frans Salo. B.C. Ont., 1946-1957; 7 items (Reel 24)
      - from: August Koski. B.C., 1958-1969; 6 items (Reel 24)
  - Tampere
    - Aini Sinisalo
      - from: Selma Julin, Ellen Ilvander. Calif., 1964; 7 items (Reel 24)
    - Taina Ruissalo
      - from: Aino Jankon. Ont., Fla., 1964; 8 items (Reel 24)
  - Turku
    - Frans Uusilehto
      - from: Ellen Salonen. Wash. (.27 items), 1946-1955 (Reel 24)
      - from: Tyyne Kangas. Wash., 1954-1955; 2 items (Reel 24)
      - from: Ellen Ranta. Wash., 1950-1953; 3 items (Reel 24)
    - Elsa Rutanen
      - from: Lyyli Oberg. Mass., 1947-1964; 17 items (Reel 24)
      - from: Auni Narva. Ill., 1950-1951; 13 items (Reel 24)
      - from: Rauha Ilmonen. Cal., 1953-1963; 13 items (Reel 24)
    - Norma Salminen
      - from: Hannes Renfors. Minn., 1959; 12 items (Reel 24)
      - from: J. Pietila. Minn., 1960; 1 items (Reel 24)
- Late arrivals:, letters to
  - Kiikka parish
    - Wilho Yli-Tuina
      - from: Wiktor Yli-Tuina, Oskar Yli-Tuina. Minn., 1955-1963; 12 items (Reel 25)
    - Kiikkas Cooperative Bank
      - from: various.
        - Finland, Minn., Mont., Idaho, Wash., 1907-1916; 42 items (Reel 25)
        - Negaunee, Mich., undated; 4 items (Reel 25)
        - Minn., Wash., 1910-1914; 6 items (Reel 25)
  - Luvia parish
    - Anna Homeri
      - from: Albert Bergstrom. B.C., Fin, 1924-1961; 112 items (Reel 25)
  - Merikarvia parish
    - Juho Romppanen
      - from: Jenny Salonen. Calif., Ont., Ill., 1939-1962; 7 items (Reel 25)
  - Ulvila parish
    - Aina Suominen
      - from: Miina Olson. S.D., 1929-1958; 39 items (Reel 25)
      - from: Hilkka-Liisa Toivola. Ont., Wash., 1952-1964; 148 items (Reel 25)